Okay the next step that we're going to do is we've used the different parts of the nebulizer and we're going to do a cleaning.
You need to do this between, every time that you use a nebulizer.
So I know sometimes with my children it would be a couple of times a day.
You want to take it apart first by disengaging the hose from the other components of the nebulizer.
Again as I mentioned earlier, do not wash the hose, don't do anything with it, you don't ever want to get any kind of water in here because that could, if it doesn't dry properly it could lead to an infection, so you definitely don't want to do anything with the hose.
Only replace it when it starting to get worn or torn.
The other parts what we're going to do is we're just going to take regular clean tap water.
I've got some dish detergent that you use to wash your dishes with, you want to use a non lemon.
The lemon kind of detergent could be something that might weaken the materials that are getting washed, the plastic.
Put them in there.
You don't necessarily have to soak them for any great deal, you're just going to be rinsing them just good so that they're getting a nice cleaning with the soapy water.